filmlinc.org 2014-05-18

# Privacy Policy | Filmlinc.com | Film Society of Lincoln Center

The Film Society of Lincoln Center, Inc. ("Film Society") knows that users of its web site care about the personal information they provide to us. This privacy policy, which is part of our overall Terms and Conditions of Use, is designed to provide you with information about how we collect, store and use personally identifiable information obtained through our web site. We refer to this information as "personal information." Film Society reserves the right to revise this privacy policy from time to time, and by using the Film Society web site, you are agreeing to the terms of the then-current privacy policy.

##  How Information Is Collected

When you register for or wish to utilize certain of our web site services, we will ask you for information such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, certain demographic information and (if needed) credit card information. We need certain information in order to register you as a unique user and let you access personalized services. However, other requested information is optional and can be given at your discretion.

Like most web sites, Film Society uses "cookies." A "cookie" is a text file, invoked by standard browser software, that we place on your hard drive to enable our systems to, among other things, recognize your browser, track transactions, and allow you to navigate our web site without having to re-enter information. The information gathered by cookies is not made available to organizations. We may also automatically receive and store certain other types of information, such as the type of web browser you use or the pages you follow links to from the Film Society web site.

##  Use Of Information We Collect

Personal information collected through this web site may be used by Film Society to communicate with you, register you as a user, allow purchasing and shipping of tickets, subscriptions, memberships and/or merchandise, enable you to participate in special promotions and to navigate the web site without having to re-enter information, administer our web site, comply with applicable law, and as otherwise provided in this privacy policy. We may occasionally make personal information available to select other organizations, including but not limited to, non-profit arts organizations, affiliated organizations, agents working on our behalf, companies or organizations with whom we have a contractual or sponsor relationship, or in connection with an asset transfer. We may also provide aggregated data to these and other organizations. Although we may make reasonable inquiries to determine that such other organizations maintain web site privacy policies comparable to ours, we are not responsible for the enforcement of such policies.

Certain of our programs use personal information to send updates and notices to registered users via e-mail. If you provide your mailing address or telephone number, Film Society may also use your personal information to contact you by mail or by telephone regarding special offers from Film Society, updated information about Film Society or the Film Society web site, and new services offered by Film Society. If you wish to be removed from this contact list, you may do so by contacting Film Society directly. (See the "Whom To Contact If You Have Questions" section below).

##  Third-Party Service Providers

Film Society may engage reputable third-party vendors in order to help us manage our web site and allow us to better service our visitors and customers. These may include third-party vendors engaged to analyze, for marketing purposes, the information collected on our web site.

Film Society's site may contain links to third-party web sites. Once you leave Film Society's web site, this privacy policy will not apply to such web sites.

##  Administration Of Our Web Site / Compliance With Law

We may disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms and Conditions of Use or to protect the safety, property or other rights of our users or the public. In addition, we may disclose or access account information for administrative and other purposes that we believe are necessary to develop, maintain, and improve our products and services. We also may disclose your personal information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process.

##  Security Used To Protect Your Information

We take commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of customer information via a variety of access controls, including password protection, electronic firewalls, and data encryption. However, Film Society does not guarantee the security of such information.

##  Other Organizations Featured On Our Web Site

We may provide links to other web sites, but Film Society is not responsible for the privacy policies, terms and conditions of use, or content of any such web sites. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and terms and conditions of use of linked web sites. You may agree to provide personal information to other companies who provide content for various parts of our web site. If you agree to provide information to such companies, that information will be subject to their privacy policies.

##  Children Under Thirteen Years of Age

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under thirteen years of age.

##  Changes to Privacy Policy

Film Society may revise its privacy policy from time to time. We encourage you to visit this page periodically to review our current policy so that you will always know what information we gather and how we may use that information.
